geoiq.com 2012-05-22

# Privacy | GeoIQ

At FortiusOne(GeoIQ), we know that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By accessing FortiusOne website properties ("Website") (GeoIQ.com, FortiusOne.com, GeoCommons.com, and any others owned by FortiusOne), or using any of the services provided through the Website you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?**

This Privacy Policy covers FortiusOne's treatment of personal information that FortiusOne gathers when you are on the Websites or any website owned and operated by FortiusOne, or when you use the Websites services.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to content you post or otherwise make available to other users or the public via the website. You acknowledge that any Website display name (if you have one) may be displayed to other users when you post content. Any content that you submit to the Website may be widely redistributed through the Internet and other media channels.

This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that FortiusOne does not own or control, or to individuals that FortiusOne does not employ or manage.

**Website Visitors**

FortiusOne collects non-personally-identifying information including the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. FortiusOne's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how the Websites visitors use each site. From time to time, FortiusOne may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to FortiusOne's websites choose to interact with the Websites in ways that require FortiusOne to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that FortiusOne gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we may ask customers who want save or upload data to register with a username and email address on the Website. Those who engage in transactions with FortiusOne may be asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, FortiusOne collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the customer's interaction with FortiusOne. FortiusOne does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain activities.

In addition, we may combine non-personally-identifiable information with personally-identifiable information in a manner that enables us to attribute Website usage to an individual customer's computer or corporate network.   We do so, however, only for our own internal business purposes and will not share such combined data with third parties without your permission.  In some instances, FortiusOne may highlight a subset of this combined data on FortiusOne websites for marketing purposes.  This would not include personally-identifying information and would enable FortiusOne to showcase user groups, networks and high-volume contributors to FortiusOne's GeoCommons public website.  

**Aggregated Statistics**

FortiusOne may collect statistics which may be comprised of aggregated personally-identifying information about the behavior of visitors to its websites and customers of its services. FortiusOne may display this statistical information publicly or provide it to others. However, FortiusOne does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

FortiusOne discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on FortiusOne's behalf or to provide services available at FortiusOne's websites and services, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using FortiusOne's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. FortiusOne will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, FortiusOne discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, court order, or when FortiusOne believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of FortiusOne, third parties or the public at large.

**Communications**

If you are a registered member of a FortiusOne website and have supplied your email address, FortiusOne may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with FortiusOne and our products. We primarily use our corporate blog and website to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you are a registered member of a FortiusOne website and do not wish to receive such emails, please follow the instructions included in each email sent. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. FortiusOne takes measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. FortiusOne uses cookies to help FortiusOne identify and track visitors, their usage of the Websites, and their website access preferences. FortiusOne visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using FortiusOne's websites, with the drawback that certain features of FortiusOne's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

FortiusOne may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in FortiusOne's sole discretion. FortiusOne encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If changes are made, notice will be given in the FortiusOne blog. Your continued use of our sites and services after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**Questions**

FortiusOne's full contact information, including location, may be found on our Contact page.

**Creative Commons**

This Privacy Policy document is derived from the privacy policy published by [http://www.swivel.com](http://www.swivel.com/ "http://www.swivel.com") and is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 2.5 License.
